Why am I always [music] in front of the
whole
like
Can you show me Yowie?
Yeah.
Have you seen this one? [music]
Yes, I have.
World.
Guys, it's time for a haul of
everything.
>> [music]
>> I'm going to the mall and I've got my
man's card. Today, I am basically going
to be a sugar baby. So, I'm going to
pretend like I'm shopping, like I'm back
in the 2000s with the old Victoria's
Secret and like when the malls were
actually fun to go to when you'd get a
little drink and you drink it. And like
we're going to Barnes & Noble's. We're
going to Sephora. We're going to
Victoria's Secret. Oh my god. Also,
we're going to go to Cheesecake Factory.
Cheesecake Factory is like so 2000s
Tuscan vibes. I love Cheesecake Factory
and I haven't been in so long. I'm so
excited. I have literally I haven't been
shopping for like months. I've I haven't
bought any new makeup this year and I
haven't like restocked on anything. So,
we're basically restocking all my makeup
and getting all the makeup that has been
on my wish list for so long and I've got
such a 2000s fit on. I've got my vintage
Halston Oh, it's also like super cold
for some reason in California. It's been
raining. I know like it's winter for a
lot of people right now and there's like
snowstorms and like trees are exploding,
but California has literally been sunny
and um can't relate like oh
And I've got this super adorable little
top and to make it even more 2000s I've
got this gold coach bag cuz that's just
like a screams 2000s. I don't know.
Also, my mom said that this is fake. I
thrifted it, so I don't care. You're not
a fashion girl if you
Actually, I can't say anything about
that cuz it's like you can be a fashion
girl however you want. Care if you want,
but I don't. It's going to be like a
girls shopping day like me and you. He's
my the man is not going to be in the
video. Okay, don't worry. That's scary.
That's scary. Why is a man there? Don't
worry. It's going to be me and you
shopping together and using his card.
Basically, sugar baby. I have this like
entire list on my phone of the things
that I need to get.
Wait, what the [\h__\h] This is my entire
list.
Oh, that's it. It looks a little short,
but like I swear it's so long.
Got to make sure that we smell good.
Oh my
And I'm going to use vanilla cashmere on
my hair.
This is the outfit.
We're driving right now and we're going
to go to the MAC store. I think I'm
going to spend the most at the MAC store
because there's a lot of things that
I've been wanting to get.
Shut up. I'm I'm kind of scared to go to
MAC because I know there's literally
going to be one girl and they're like
helping us the whole time and like kind
of monitoring us and I don't really I
hate that and I don't know. I just like
have a lot of things to look at. I have
like a lot of things to look at and I
don't really want to be bothered. So,
yeah, I'm a little scared that I won't
be able to record in there either, too.
>> [music]
>> These are all the swatches that we did.
I think I
I'm going to restock on whirl cuz I lost
that one.
I lost this one.
Whirl.
>> [music]
[music]
>> We secured the MAC bag. I'm not sure if
I should do a haul at the end of the
video or if I should just show you what
I'm getting
as I'm getting it. These are the ones
that we got. This was so pretty that I
just wanted it. It's a lip gloss in the
shade dreamy. It's like sparkly and I
kind of want to put it on right now.
It's so sparkly and cute. I want to put
on whirl right now cuz this is what I
wanted to put on this morning, but I
couldn't cuz I didn't have it. Whirl is
genuinely the perfect shade color for
me. I love when it's like fresh out the
package and it's so sharp.
And now we're going to head to Barnes &
Noble's.
And then there's the cafe there.
Hi.
Maybe I'll get a little movie, too or
Did you not capture me saying that I
wanted to read it? No, cuz I I remember
thinking
I'm about to beat this [\h__\h] up. Stop.
Oh my god. We'll just redo it.
>> Well, I said that I was thinking about
getting the Harry Potter books cuz they
seemed interesting
to read and it's yeah. Are you going to
capture me going all in the books? I'm
showing the title. This guy does not
know how to film. He didn't for this.
He's getting everything in the world
except for me. When did [music] you
train me? I woke up and boom, I was a
cameraman. SHUT YOUR [\h__\h] MOUTH.
OKAY.
I FEEL LIKE ALL OF THE BOOKS THAT I'm
reading are just young adult. I'm too
stupid to actually read something that's
like like actually of substance.
Like Twilight. Like Twilight and like
Gossip Girl and like And he did rivalry.
Yeah, I'm going to read that next. I'm
looking for Pretty Little Liars. Oh
wait, I think I just found it. No.
That's not it. Pretty Little Liars Let's
read CELESTIAL MONSTER.
HEY, PRETTY LITTLE LIARS.
THOSE ARE BOOKS IN SPANISH.
OH.
OH, OKAY. Look at this. Can we read
this?
I did not know they had Five Nights at
Freddy's books. The official movie
novel.
Oh.
Ew. Wait, what? This is not canon, is
it?
Not canon.
I think the books are actually How is it
canon if it's unofficial and just
fan-made? This is not unofficial. It's
by Scott Cawthon himself. Oh, okay.
Yeah. I don't know anything about that.
on We got the Gossip
We got the Gossip Girl book.
XOXO and they did not have Pretty Little
Liars, unfortunately.
>> [sighs]
>> I'm probably not going to get this cuz
the cover is so ugly.
Poor them.
They changed the freaking Wuthering
Heights cover to this freaking [\h__\h]
But I kind of Ew, I don't like that they
have this on there.
Anyways.
We got the cutest little Totoro stuff.
Ooh.
I think we're going to look at this the
DVDs now
because I don't think there's anything
that I'm going to get. I don't think I'm
going to get this cuz I don't like the
cover.
And yeah.
Hopefully, there's a little something in
the test.
I think if they have The Office, I want
to get another season of The Office cuz
I'm going through it like crazy.
I don't know if they'll have it though.
They probably won't.
I'm in your favorite section.
I recommend it. Oh my god. Dirty Deeds,
really good. Oh, this one's even better.
I formed a MILF party. Oh my gosh. with
his mom.
Wow.
>> It's really good.
Can you show me Yowie?
Yeah.
I'll just say that out loud.
Come on.
We're in his home.
I kind of want to read this note cuz
it's so far. Look at him. You should
read it. The library has it. They do?
Mhm. [\h__\h] What do you Check in the
library every day?
I wish I
had the black. Guys, I don't think we're
going to get anything. Dang it. I really
wanted to get a little book and like get
a little drink cuz usually sometimes
they have like a little coupon after you
buy something like for the cafe, but
yeah.
Not going to get anything. So, I think
we're going to move on now. Dang it.
I'll probably buy it online or something
or go to the library to check it out.
Perfect spot.
Why am I always in front of the whole
like
You just have good taste like here.
You don't choose.
Okay.
I did.
>> [laughter]
>> You need it? Yeah.
Hey.
Yeah. yeah.
Is this your son? Yeah, it's my son.
Hey guys.
You can't look at Barnes & Noble's
without looking at the trinkets.
Oh.
Where you going?
Excuse me.
Oh, look at that. Excuse me.
Why are you running?
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, I decided to get um a drink here
because I realized that they have the
sugar cookie in this area in in Oh my
god. I'm going to be careful.
>> [laughter]
>> Where we live, like all the Starbucks
near there, they don't have sugar cookie
anywhere, but they still have it here.
So, I was like, okay, let me get a drink
cuz the sugar cookie is so good, I
swear. And Johnny got a pizza pretzel. I
like the stuff that they have at Barnes
& Noble's cuz they have like stuff that
they don't have at regular Starbucks.
>> They even have grilled cheese. I know.
They have grilled cheese. They got like
chocolate cake and stuff. It's crazy
over here.
Oh, it just looks so Yeah.
pepper leaves in it. It smells good
though.
>> Mhm.
I think it's really hot.
Oh my god, it's so good. Is it? I told
Yeah, I totally forgot what the flavor
was like.
He's not even focusing on the food. Oh.
He's going to your phone. Oh my god. Go.
Oh. It looks so yummy.
What is this, an ad?
I didn't get copyrighted. Oh, we got our
little drink and snack from Starbucks
and now we're going to go to the mall
and do the real shopping. I'm excited
cuz we're also going to get Cheesecake
Factory there. And the Cheesecake
Factory is so Tuscan vibes. I love it in
there and I want a diet Coke so bad. And
I might get some calamari. I don't know
if I can handle that at the moment cuz
my wisdom teeth are still healing. I'll
see you guys at the mall.
We're at the mall now and me and Johnny
were having a conversation actually
about whether it's okay for guys to
thirst [clears throat] trap or not. And
we both think it's weird if guys like
thirst trap and like take photos of
themselves and stuff, but like it's okay
if girls do it. It's I don't know. What
was your opinion, Johnny? It just it's
just wrong. It's just wrong.
>> don't think it's something like you're
taking time out of your day and you're
like, let me take some pics real quick.
Yeah, I would never date a guy that
takes pics of himself and like has a
dedicated Instagram or like a TikTok
page of just himself thirst trapping and
like taking hot selfies. Like that's and
especially if he has a high following
account. That's something you want to
avoid, ladies. Okay.
Fine dining for the sugar baby. For the
skinnylicious.
>> Johnny's here for that skinnylicious
menu. We're going to get Cheesecake
Factory before going in because I don't
want to go in there with all of my bags.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, we have our pennies and we're
going to wish
for something. Okay.
No guns, so make sure you don't have
your stuff.
>> okay. I'll make sure.
This is how the cheese is. Ooh, yum. I
said pizza. This is so good. Triple
berry blast.
Recording. I'm recording now.
>> Okay, we're at the Cheesecake Factory.
Yes. I'm excited. We're also going to
get a little cheesecake because I've
been craving one since yesterday.
Guys, cheesecake's where it's at. Yes,
people say don't take your girl to
cheesecake. People People have such a
problem with Cheesecake Factory for some
reason. Like, oh, if you he takes you to
Cheesecake Factory on the first date,
like he's not the one, but he is the one
actually cuz he knows where it's at.
This looks so good. The baked brie with
truffle honey butter has warm [music]
bread and baked brie cheese. That sounds
so good. I haven't been to Cheesecake
Factory in so long and their menu is so
big, but usually I get the grilled steak
medallions.
These are so good, but I'm not sure if I
want to get that or the pasta.
Those are tall glasses. Mhm.
I know.
Yes, my diet Coke.
I know that's what I like, sweet.
>> Ooh, I've been Oh my god. I've been
craving diet Coke so bad.
Look at that. This is the baked brie.
That looks so good.
You want to ask for some bread?
>> It has the vinaigrette already on it.
Just ate cheesecake and
our waitress she was literally the
nicest ever. I feel like Cheesecake
Factory workers, they put in overtime.
They literally do do it so good. Like
they're the nicest people ever. We're
going to go shopping now.
>> [music]
>> I don't know. Face mask too because I
don't have any. Where to make up? Oh,
wait.
They have We Bare Bear face masks.
Okay. Oh, here's the makeup.
Ooh, look at these little lashes.
Oh, some nails.
Oh, they have a bunch of little nails.
We found the makeup. This is the
>> [music]
>> the brand that I like.
I think it was
I would get this
dark brown one. Dark brown one was so
good and I wanted a black one, too.
It seems like we don't have the Oh my
god, there's the music's hella loud.
This is Zara. This is what we're
capturing. Yeah. The dying mall. Going
to Sephora now. [music]
And I have my list of things
I don't know what's broken. I think the
one that I really liked last time was
this one.
That's a pretty color. But I'm pretty
sure the one I liked was fresh. Let's
try this.
Blush seems good, too.
No, they don't have fresh.
Johnny, why do they
I'm kind of scared cuz it seems like a
lot of stuff they don't have. I'm scared
that the shopping spree is going to be
bad
because I don't cuz it seems like a lot
of stuff is gone.
So, we have to look into to like the
little things in there.
But yeah, I'm going to keep shopping.
I'm not sure if I should get this or
not.
I've been wanting one of these like
little Dior palettes for so long,
but I'm like, do I need it though? Warm
tone one or the cool tone one?
I think I might get it cuz they're out
of like a lot of stuff that I want, so
I'm like, might as well get it. Wait,
imagine they don't have it.
Now I don't know what to do. Now you
don't know what to do. Okay, cute.
Guys, why is every store like out of all
the things that we want? I think I know
why malls are dying now. It's it's
because everything that we wanted is not
there. We went into Bath & Body Works
for the strawberry pound cake and they
didn't have it. The most popular one.
Guys, make sure you have the most your
most popular item. This is why every
damn store is shutting down and this why
nobody is going to the malls anymore.
Where are we going now? Uh the
Victoria's Secret's upstairs. Okay.
Anyways, just got out of Sephora.
We actually spent more at Sephora than
we than I thought I would. So, we're
going to Victoria's Secret. Hopefully
that makes me feel better.
I'm excited for Victoria's Secret
though, actually. The vibe in there is
just so perfect and I feel so girly and
feminine.
I love it in Victoria's Secret. Yippee.
Hi guys. Hi.
Doing well yourself? Good, thanks.
Ooh, they got new sleeping shorts.
No, I think I'm okay for now. Oh.
>> I was looking for a little lanyard.
Yeah. This little dog is so cute. Should
I get this for my keys?
>> So cute. Oh, I should have gotten a
little basket. Mhm. Do they have some
fun? Ooh,
look at these socks, too. Those are so
cute. These ones. They give me like
vintage
cuz like the scrunching right here,
that's cute, honestly. They're cool.
You you to go get a basket? you?
Yes. All right. Here you go. Here you
go.
This is what I came for.
Cute.
Rich honey.
Warm and cozy.
Please tell me they have it. I'm so
scared because I didn't see the brown
sugar one. I came for the brown sugar
scent, but it was like all the way down
there. So, I was scared they didn't have
it. But yeah, I want to smell this again
to make sure that I like it.
Yes.
I want to make sure you got my
attention now.
Mhm. That smells so good.
Mhm.
Smells like cookies.
>> Mhm.
That's really good. Okay, I'm
definitely getting one of these.
And also
buttery sugary. That's This one's brown
[music] sugar. I swear they had a scent
of this one, but they must have ran out.
Want to smell this.
I'm not sure.
I don't really like to buy lotions cuz I
don't even wear it.
Oh.
Yes. Smell this.
>> Buttery sugar? Yeah. It was either I
smelled brown sugar or buttery sugar.
>> I don't know. Brown sugar is kind of
hard to beat. Yeah.
I'm not sure about this one. Can you
smell it?
No. Okay, yeah. The brown sugar is way
better.
>> A lot. I feel like a lot of the
Victoria's Secret scents, like the
vanilla, it's like coconuty. I don't
want coconut in my vanilla. I want
vanilla vanilla.
You know what I mean? Like when you open
up a vanilla extract bottle, you smell
it, that's the vanilla that I want. Not
coconut.
I I would buy coconut.
Perfect. They've got some new food
covers.
You guys doing okay in here? Yeah. Thank
you.
I like the leopard print one.
But I wish that this part was black,
too. Mhm. Cuz I don't like
I'm like that.
I've been looking for a little lanyard
for my keys.
So, I might get one of these.
I like the stripes.
I saw they had a black one. This one's
cute.
Spiced vanilla cream.
Iced.
Spiced horchata.
Vanilla swirl.
All these are open.
Guys, it's time for a haul of everything
that we got. Mostly got a bunch of
makeup.
I feel like it looks like that I didn't
get a lot, but I swear that I did
because this little bag holds like over
a hundred dollars worth of product in
it. Like why does it look like so small?
I feel like I should be getting like a
big bag, you know? The haul looks small,
but it's big. I swear. I'm honestly
still a little bit sad that [music] we
didn't get anything from Barnes & Noble.
It's so weird that a lot of places were
out of stuff. Like how? It's your job to
Okay, whatever. I'm not going to sound
like a freaking Karen, but like this is
why malls are dying, like I said before.
Cuz why is everything out of stock? I
don't I don't get it. I don't get it. It
was dead in there, which I'm glad
because I was able to record, but also
like what happened to going to [music]
malls for fun? Like going to malls after
school, the art of shopping, okay? It's
an art form. So, we couldn't get
anything from Barnes & Nobles and we
couldn't get anything from Bath & Body
Works. I was literally just going to get
that little car thing. It smells so
good. Please get that. It's so amazing.
What should we start with? I think I
might do Victoria's Secret in the
middle. I'll do
MAC first. We got a bunch of lip stuff
from MAC. For the lip liners, I got
Sweet Talk, which I'm wearing right now,
and I got Whirl because I keep losing
it, and I got a lipstick in the shade
Gel. The shade is so pretty. I don't
know if it's going to show up on my
hand, but like it's like shimmery.
Girl, you can't see it. [music] There
you go. It's like a shimmery color. I
love it. Then I got this beautiful lip
gloss. Look at that. This shade is
dreamy. Like I literally could not get
[music] this. I couldn't not get this.
I'm not even a lip gloss girl. I don't
like lip gloss. I like the sleek satin
lipsticks, but I I like like a creamy
lipstick, but like a gloss is sometimes
like it's too much for me cuz it gets in
your hair and stuff, but this was just
so beautiful, so cute and glittery.
I'm obsessed. And then I got this little
crayon, the dazzle crayon, so you can
put it on your lips or your eyes and
stuff. I think I have a swatch of it
ready [music] right there.
It's like shimmery cute. That is all
that I got from MAC because I had a lot
initially. It looks different in person,
which is why I'm glad to go in person
instead of online. [\h__\h] my battery is
running out. Also, I just want to say my
boobs look really [\h__\h] good today.
Like today my boobs looked the best they
have ever looked. I know you guys are
looking.
How does it feel being caught?
How does it feel? I know y'all were
looking, but they do look good. They
look really [\h__\h] good today. And I
think like I've gained weight, so that's
why my tits look humongous, too.
Anyways, here's what I got at Sephora.
I'm a little bit sad because the one
thing that I came for that I literally
waited months to get was not [music]
there.
I don't even care, but since they didn't
have some of the things I was going to
get, I decided to splurge
and get
the Dior Backstage palette, the iconic
Pinterest
palette. And I haven't even opened it up
yet. Look. It's shiny. It's reflective.
This is so bougie. This [\h__\h] was
fifty-five dollars. Without this
palette, I would have spent more at MAC
than at Sephora. I really did think I
was going to spend more at MAC. I
thought I was going to spend like three
hundred dollars at MAC, but some of the
stuff turned out to be not as cute in
person. How the hell do I open this?
First time unboxing.
>> [music]
>> Look at
this.
Now that I have my nails, too.
Oh my god, it's so pretty.
This is the iconic Pinterest on
everyone's Pinterest board makeup
palette. Oh my god, it's so beautiful. I
love the colors. I feel like a makeup
look with all these colors in it. I
literally I'm so obsessed. It's so cute
and bougie bougie. Just aesthetic. It's
so aesthetic. Like I'm I don't want to
even want to use it because it's so
cute. This makes me so happy. Now I can
put this [\h__\h] in my thumbnails without
it just being clickbait. I actually I
actually got it. I got this heat
protectant spray. I'm going to be trying
it out. I don't know if it's good, but I
heard it's good. I don't even know what
I've heard about this. It could be bad.
I could have actually heard that it's
bad and thought it I thought I heard I
don't know. I just keep seeing it
everywhere and I'm like, "Okay, I guess
I buy it now." Just feel like the one
that I've been using is not doing [\h__\h]
cuz why is my hair falling out? Got this
and it's the extra big. It's extra big.
A size matters. We got this Makeup
Forever little white liner. I wanted to
use it for like my inner corners to
highlight it more. And then lastly, I
got I just refilled on my baking setting
powder.
The Huda Beauty one is my favorite one.
I have tried the Fit Me powder. That
shit's not good. I don't know who is
spreading this misinformation, but that
[\h__\h] was so cakey and bad. Y'all Y'all
are probably like, "You shouldn't even
be talking, bitch." I I don't know. It
just didn't work for me, but this one it
worked pretty well and I really like it.
And I need to show you guys what I got
at Miniso. Pretty sure you know what I
got. I got these two eyeliners. They are
felt tip liners, but I usually get the
pencil one. They didn't have the pencil
one. Once again, they don't they don't
have the things that I want. So, yeah. I
just got the felt tip ones cuz I'm like,
"Okay, whatever." I like pencil a lot
better because I really like to get the
[\h__\h] in there in my inner corners and
like do that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] But I'm
trying out these cuz I'm like, "Okay, I
need something." And I really like this
brand. It's an It's like a Asian brand
and I feel like it's really good for me
because I'm half Asian and it stays on.
I have the mascara and that [\h__\h] is so
waterproof. I will literally go in the
shower and my mascara is not gone at
all. It's literally still on there. Last
but not least are Victoria's Secret.
Okay, this
These are so [snorts] cute.
Like why is everything
like so color coordinated actually in my
Victoria's Secret haul. I got a bunch of
little lip glosses. These are all the
lip glosses that I got. This color was
so cute. It's Candy Baby. It's like the
perfect cute like baby pink. This one is
like a shimmery one. And this one it's a
gingerbread lip. It's kind of brown.
[music]
And then I got this caramel one. It's
glittery and it's so cute. These colors
are so adorable. Like look at that. They
go together so well. This is aesthetic.
This is what I came to the freaking mall
for. I wanted to go on my shopping spree
because I wanted [music] this brown
sugar body mist. It smells so
It smells so good. It's so good.
What does it smell like? Well, it smells
like brown sugar, but it smells like
It smells a very warm. It's not vanilla.
Can't even describe it. It just smells
so good. It's a sweet like bakery smell.
Oh my god, it's like reminding me of
like Barnes & Noble and like a sweet
treat. Oh my god, it smells so good.
Last thing, we got this lanyard for my
keys because I have a freaking Minecraft
thingy on my keys and I'm like, "Okay, I
need to upgrade. I kind of want to be
more aesthetic." So, I got this little
Victoria's Secret lanyard. [music] And
that is basically all that we got. This
haul is literally so cute and my
favorite. They're all like matching
colors. So cute. And that is everything
that we got on our shopping spree. Thank
you guys for watching. Even though they
were out of some of the things that I
really wanted, I had a lot of fun
shopping and pretending like I was back
in the 2000s. Honestly, Cheesecake
Factory was so lit. It was lit as [\h__\h]
And there the baked brie was so good. Oh
my god, please try that. It's It was so
good. Oh my god. I'm going to go back to
Cheesecake Factory regularly. That [\h__\h]
rocked my world. Hello. Anyways, thank
you guys for watching. I hope you like
the video. See you in the next one.